Nikunj Rohitkumar Shah

Phone: +91 6355489110

Email: nikunjsbit@gmail.com

Address: B-85 Swami Residency Behind-Air Force Station, Makarpura, Vadodara - 390014, (Gujarat)

Summary

I have specialized in front-end development. And now I am working as a Full Stack developer. Experienced with all stages of the development of dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous technologies and tools HTML5, JavaScript, CSS, MySQL, MSSQL, MongoDB, Angular, Laravel Asp.net MVC, Asp.Net Web-API, and Nodejs. I am ready to learn new technology and tools. I am ready to learn new technology and tools

Skill Highlights

Angular:- I can create a fresh project by installing angular and nodejs , and creating a component, services, and integrating API and performing differentTasks.Convert HTML into the angular component. Also, work with typescript the angular as off now I am working with typescript with angular

Laravel: - During working as a full stack developer I also create a backend in Laravel at the basic level and create an API init., so, therefore, I know the basics of Laravel, install Laravel, composer, used PHP artisan command (Note: Do don't have hand-onexperience).

Nodejs:- As a developer learning new technology is required and my company allows me to learn the Nodejs, so thereforee I start learning Nodejs, I learn installation, and create API basics using MVC structure. (Note:Do don't have hand-onexperience)

Asp.Net : -As a full stack developer also working onn asp.net webAPI. I know how to createe MVC projects and web API

Database: - MSSQL, MYSQL MongoDB (basics)

Tools:- GitHub, Bitbuckets, Trello, Slack, Jira

Other Technologies:- DOPWIZARD, basic of Java

Experience

Total Experince(3.3 year)

Web -design –(Work with different company, Most working on theme customizing for 1 years)

During work with this different company I have theme customizing and basic of html,

CSS, bootstrap ,basic JS.

Full Stack developer — Vagisa technology (Angular+Asp.net web API, Asp.net mcv, NodeJS) from (23/3/2021-10-6-2022) During work the Vagisa technology, I got in-depth knowledge of angular and also how to work in MVC project and web API

Full Stack developer – Srishti innovative (Angular) from (13/06/2022-15/12/2022) During work the Srishti innovative ,I got in-depth knowledge of angular and also software and better understanding of integrating API perform the logics

Senior Software developer – Uni-abroad (Angular & laravel)(5/12/2022-20/3/2023) During work the – Uni-abroad,I got in-depth

knowledge of angular and also how to work in MVC project and web API

Angular developer(Freelancing) – lan4 Solution (Angular)(01/06/2023 -01/07/2023) During work the – lane 4 solution, I work with UI were I have to integrate the HTML,CSS part into angular and create the angular component according to requirement and also solved the bugs onsite UI bugs , also create API in NodeJS and Laravel , solve the API bugs and test API, then integrate the API by create the end-point service and perform the logic according to design and SRS(System Requirement Specification document given to me)

Note: I don't have hand-on experience in node js and laravel but I create the API in both technology by doing the re-search and development

Education

DEGREE	YEAR	NAMEOFINSTITUTE	UNIVERSITY /BOARD	СРІ
B.E (CSE)	2017	Babaria Institute of Technology	Gujarat Technological University	6.46
Diploma (CE)	2014	Sigma Institute of Engineering and Technology	Gujarat Technological University	6.29
SSC	2008	YANSHY HIGH SCOOL	Gujarat board (GSEB)	57%

Personal Details

Date of Birth 8 February 1990

Sex Male

Nationality Indian

Hobbies Movies, Reading books

Marital Status Unmarried Hindu(jain)